<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Van Le</title>
    <link>https://hellovanle.com/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Van Le</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hellovanle.com/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Business Analytical Writing: Thailand’s Growing Battle with Childhood Obesity: A Wake-Up Call</title>
      <link>https://hellovanle.com/portfolio/business-analytical-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellovanle.com/portfolio/business-analytical-writing/</guid>
      <description>Visualization Python (Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly) for graphs, charts, and world map, InDesign, Power Point Data wrangling Python, SQL, and Excel Disclaimer
This project is a personal initiative aimed at showcasing my critical thinking and analytical abilities using various programming languages and tools. This project is not intended to provide professional advice or endorse any particular viewpoint. The information contained in this project is for informational purposes only.
Obesity rates have risen in every country around the world since 1975 The number of obese adults has seen a substantial increase globally between 1975 and 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obesity in Thailand</title>
      <link>https://hellovanle.com/portfolio/obesity-final/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellovanle.com/portfolio/obesity-final/</guid>
      <description>Click here to view this notebook in full screen </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pet Choy Rebranding</title>
      <link>https://hellovanle.com/portfolio/pet-choy-rebranding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellovanle.com/portfolio/pet-choy-rebranding/</guid>
      <description>Our Story As a co-founder of Pet Choy, a pet food startup with a mission to improve pet wellness and rights, I embarked on a journey to create a brand that would make a positive impact on the lives of pets in Vietnam. After three months of successful launch, I organized a networking event to gather feedback from our customers. While their pets loved our food, I learned that cost was a significant factor in their purchasing decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sole Food E-commerce platform</title>
      <link>https://hellovanle.com/portfolio/sole-food-e-commerce-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellovanle.com/portfolio/sole-food-e-commerce-platform/</guid>
      <description>Overview As part of a UX program at UCI, a team of three classmates: Van Le, Julia Kang and Matt Janke was assigned to create a UX/UI redesign for a non-profit. The team selected Sole Food Street Farms, a non-profit dedicated to empowering individuals with limited resources through job opportunities, agricultural training, and community support. The assignment was completed in two weeks and aimed to improve the organization’s user experience and design.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
